<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.chapternotify" name="Chapter Notify" version="0.7.1" provider-name="Rouzax">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Show chapter notifications during video playback</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Displays a styled overlay notification when a new chapter starts playing in videos from configured library folders. Designed for concert recordings and festival DJ sets with named chapters (Artist - Track [Label]). Perfect companion to CrateDigger, which embeds chapter markers from 1001Tracklists.</description>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
    <source>https://github.com/Rouzax/service.chapternotify</source>
    <news>v0.7.1 (2026-04-14)
- Fixed festival set overlays showing only the raw track title instead of the full Artist / Track / Label layout
- Chapter Notify now reads chapter names directly from the MKV file, picking the English-language display string that CrateDig embeds alongside the plain title entry

v0.7.0 (2026-04-09)
- Added "Show record label" setting so the overlay can hide the record label line on demand
- Overlay now picks panel height to match its content: 3-line, 2-line, or single-line
- Raw chapters that do not match the "Artist - Track [Label]" format render as a clean centered single line instead of an awkward partial 3-line box
- Fixed the historical reversed labeling: the top row in the overlay now correctly says "Track:" (was internally swapped in v0.5.0 through v0.6.0)

v0.6.0 (2026-04-08)
- Added Manual and Both trigger modes - the chapter overlay can now be summoned on demand by pressing a configurable key during playback
- Added Trigger settings group with Mode, Trigger key (free-form text input), and Remove keymap binding action
- Manual trigger bypasses the library path filter, so chapter info can be summoned on any media that has chapters
- Each press of the trigger key always shows or replaces the overlay for visible feedback. To dismiss manually, press any other key
- Default trigger_mode is Auto so existing v0.5.1 behavior is preserved on upgrade

v0.5.1 (2026-04-07)
- Fixed text descenders overlapping the accent separator line
- Improved vertical spacing between all text lines
    </news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
